Hey everybody, Packers national scout
Mike Owen joins us. And Mike, thanks for
your time during a busy time. And tell
me about Brandon Sisay, the cornerback
out of South Carolina, that you made
your pick in the second round. Yeah,
Sisay I like a lot. You know, he's got
size, got good athleticism, quick feet,
can run. The big thing, he's smart,
tough, and physical. Speaking of which,
is that his football personality, tough
and physical? Yeah, he's tough and
physical. He plays with a chip on his
shoulder. He's had that,
you know, whole career that I've known
about him. And he's wired right, you
know, at the end of day. Good football
character, good personal character.
[music]
Dude loves football, film junkie.
Is he the type [music] of player
that's going to come in and make you
better? And I'm not saying starting
instantly, but will he make somewhere,
somehow, make the Green Bay Packers
better? Yep, that's why we selected him,
you [music] know. He's a good football
player, like I said, wired right and
stuff. So, biggest thing for him is come
in here, be the best version of himself,
create competition [music] within that
corner room, and elevate himself and the
rest of the group. Elevate together. And
in that regard, do you see him lining up
immediately, like on the outside, in the
slot? [music]
What kind of player is he that way? I
think he has the ability to play both
inside [music] and outside. You know,
I'll leave that up to the defensive
staff, but I would guess he'd be an
outside guy, but he has the flexibility
to play both.